# Nahiduzzaman Badhon



+880 1685835483

24 November 1995

badhon100.github.io

github.com/Badhon100

in linkedin.com/in/nahiduzzaman-badhon-93718098



# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Diverse work experience including programming, and organizer. Extensive knowledge of software development life cycle as well as proficiency in some programming languages. Willing to use my skills, technologies that I am familiar with, innovative thoughts that will benefit the organization.

# **EXPERIENCE**

o Flutter Developer

MeekTec IT

04/2021 - present

**Activities** 

- Develop in-house project
- Maintain developed project
- o Flutter Trainer

Wizard Software and Technology

Bangladesh

10/2021 - 31/01/2022

#### **Activities**

- Teaching students about dart programming language.
- Teaching students about Flutter frameworks
- Teaching Students to build mobile applications.

o Software Development Internship

Zaman IT

05/2019 - 09/2019

#### **Activities**

- Build E-commerce website with PHP
- Participated in on-the-job training with senior programmers
- Experienced with solo and team projects

## **EDUCATION**

o BSc in Computer Science and Engineering

IUBAT - International University of Business Agriculture and

Technology 05/2015 -09/2019

**CGPA:** 3.43 out of 4.00

Higher Secondary Certificate

Safiuddin Sarker Academy and College Session: 2011 – 2014

Major in Science **GPA:** 4.20 out of 5.00

Secondary School Certificate

Shahajuddin Sarker Model School& College

Session: 2009 - 2011

Major in Science **GPA:** 5.00 out of 5.00

## PROFESSIONAL PROFICIENCY

- o Programming Languages: Java, SQL, JavaScript, C++, Dart
- o Framework: Flutter
- o Solid background in mathematics, analysis, and problem-solving
- o Ability to write code by following SOLID principles
- o Unit test, Debugging, Documentation
- o Github, Restful API, Firebase

## **PROJECTS**

## To Do

- An android mobile app to keep to dolist
- ➤ Keep to do list in category wise
- > Developed by Developed using Flutter & Sqflite
- ➤ GitHub Link: <a href="https://github.com/Badhon100/todo">https://github.com/Badhon100/todo</a>

#### **Smart Phone Book**

- ➤ An android mobile app to keep records of contact
- > Share contact information by scanning QR code
- > Update profile image and other information
- > Developed using Flutter & Sqflite

#### E-commers website

- ➤ A multi-vendor e-commerce website
- > User can buy and sell products
- ➤ Developed by PHP & MySQL database
- ➤ GitHub link: https://github.com/Badhon100/RaakSaak

## REFERENCES

# Dr. Utpal kanti Das

Coordinator

Department of CSE, IUBAT

Phone: 01819199419

#### MR. Rashedul Islam

Senior Lecturer, Department of CSE, IUBAT

Phone: 017664452